Naser (vali) Rafinia

C# Developer

+98-912-725-0317 Naser.r@gmail.com www.linkedin.com/in/nrafinia https://naser.rafinia.info

Summary

Senior software developer with over 10 years of experience. By managing the team 5-member or participating in various teams, I have been able to present large and successful projects to product owners over the years. I personally consider myself a conscientious person who can achieve the best results.

SKILLS

- .Net Technologies: .Net Core, ASP.Net, MVC, Blazor, Web API
- Programming languages: C#, JavaScript, T-SQL
- Database: SQL Server, MongoDB, RavenDB
- Server-side Frameworks: REST, gRPC, JWT, MediatR
- Other: Redis, Elasticsearch, Redisearch, Entity Framework Core, Dapper
- Client-side Technologies: JavaScript, jQuery, PWA, Ajax, JSON, Knockout, HTML, CSS
- Version Control: TFS, Visual Studio Git
 - Tools: Jira, OTRS
- Hosting: IIS, Kestrel

WORK EXPERIENCE

PRINCIPAL SOFTWARE ENGINEER, Iranian Internet Marketplace, Sep 2016 - present

- Designing the structure and creating a new B2B panel of the company, which provided the possibility of 2000% sales growth for the company in the country.
- Updating the panel with microservice structure through Ocelot API Gateway, which increased the number of simultaneous users to 700 and active users to 20,000 daily users.
- Add new features to the panel, including: the possibility of buying tourist tickets for planes, buses, trains, facilities related to mobile operators, adding a store to buy goods, access control and admin section, and...
- Create a new PWA UI via Blazor
- Providing REST services for various parts to create a mobile application
- Build search engine structure with Elasticsearch to increase search output from 10 seconds to less than 0.5 second

Environment: C#, Asp.Net core 5.0, Blazor, Ocelot API Gateway, Redis, Elasticsearch, gRPC, JWT Token, MediatR, SQL Server, xUnit for Testing

SOFTWARE DEVELOPMENT MANAGER, TAK Makaron, Jul 2014 - Oct 2016

- Upgrading the single branch system of the company's current distribution and sales to several branches, which made
 it possible to use it in the country.
- Upgrading the technology and structures in the system to increase system output by 40%
- Creating a system for collecting and transferring information from branches to the head office and vice versa

Environment: C#, Windows form, WCF, ADO .Net, SQL Server, SQL row versioning

HEAD OF IT RESEARCH AND DEVELOPMENT DIVISION, Solico Group, Nov 2012 - Oct 2014

- Installation of MS Dynamics AX software and adding localization features such as solar calendar, RTL, ...
- Installation and management of Jira software along with localization such as solar calendar, RTL, ...

Environment: Java, X++ scripting language

TEAM LEAD, Mandegar Group, Jan 2012 – Jul 2012

- Due to insufficient efficiency of the financial and administrative system in the company, with the help of the team, we upgraded the system from Delphi to ASP.Net.
- Support and maintenance of the current Delphi system until the full transfer to the new version

Environment: C#, ASP.Net form, LINQ to SQL, Delphi, SQL Server

TEAM LEAD, Neda Pardaz Informatic, Apr 2010 – Jan 2012

- Create a VOIP-based financial payment system for Sepah, Mellat, and Tejarat banks
- Support and maintenance of the current Delphi-based system

Environment: C#, Windows service, Delphi, SQL Server

More experience in LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/nrafinia/

EDUCATION

ISLAMIC AZAD UNIVERSITY

Associate's Degree, Software

Licenses & Certifications

- SQL SERVER 2005 Sematec
- C# LinkedIn Assessments
- .NET FRAMEWORK LinkedIn Assessments
- TRANSACTION-SQL (T-SQL) LinkedIn Assessments

Languages

English: Limited working proficiency

Turkish: Elementary proficiency

Germany: Elementary proficiency (A1) Persian: Native